Guide to the Jerald Brauer Papers 1925-1999
University of Chicago Library
- Series IV: Divinity School. 1960-1985
  - Subseries 1: Subject Files
    - Divinity School, Spoof (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Divinity School, Statistics, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Divinity School, Accreditation, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Divinity School, Encyclopedia of Religion, 1966-1985 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Divinity School, Library Resources, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Divinity School, Deanship Correspondence, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Divinity School, Council Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Divinity School, Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Divinity School, Association, 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Divinity School, Association, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Divinity School, Doctor of Ministry Program, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Divinity School, D. Min. Program, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Divinity School, D. Min., Report, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Divinity School Council, A Documentary History (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Divinity School, Disciples Divinity House, 1956-1960 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Divinity School, Organization, 1960-1963 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Divinity School, M.Div Program, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Divinity School, M.Div Program, 1965-1969 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Divinity School Housing1956-1965 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Divinity School, Faculty Housing1960-1965 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Downtown College Self-Study, 1959-1961 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Ecumenical Institute, 1957-1962 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Engagements Declined, 1969-1970 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Equipment, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Education of Laity, n. d. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Evaluation Committee, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Faculty General, 1964-1965 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Participation, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Policy, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Committee, 1961-1964 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Bibliography, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Biographical, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Listings, 1954-1965 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Faculty News Bulletins, n. d. (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Research, 1958 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Retreats, 1962-1965 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Fellowship, 1972-1974 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Fortress Press, 1964-1980 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Field Exam Requirements, n. d. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Fund for Theological Education, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Fund for Theological Education, 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Fund for Theological Education, n. d. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Goldwasser Report, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Billy Graham, 1960-1962 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Billy Graham Center, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Health Care Conference, 1970-1974 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Health Care Conference, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Health Care Conference, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Hebrew Union College, 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - History Department, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Home Study, 1960-1964 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Howard University Press, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Humor Aging, n. d. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Inter-Future, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - International Travel Card, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Institute of Ecumenical Research, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - International Association for Liberal Christianity (IALC), 1960 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - IALC, 1964-1965 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Interseminary Committee, 1958-1963 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Internship Notes, n. d. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Internships, 1962-1964 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Japan Trip, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Japan Trip, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Jewish/Protestant Colloquium, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Conference, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Theological Seminary of America, 1965-1966 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Journal of Religion, 1974-1978 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Law School, 1957-1965 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Libraries, Science Library, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - University Libraries, Swift Library, 1959-1961 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - University Libraries, Swift Library, 1959-1961 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - University Libraries, Harper Library (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Library School, University of Chicago (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Long Range Agenda (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Long Range Planning of Divinity School Reports, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Luce Foundation, Proposal, n. d. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Lutheran World Federation, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Lutheran Church in America, 1978-1979 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Marcus Committee, 1957 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Microfilming Project, 1968-1969 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Role of the Minister, n. d. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Multicultural Institute, 1970-1972 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Murray Louis Dance Company, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1959-1965 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - National Association of Biblical Instructors, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - National Committee to Repeal the McCarren Act (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - National Council on Religion in Higher Education, 1957-1965 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - National Education Association, 1958-1961 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - National Education Association (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - New Framework for Ed. In Div Schools, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1977-1979 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - National Endowment Scholarship, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - New Plan, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - North American Conference on Theological Education, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - New Harmony Notes, n. d. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Notre Dame Center, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Office of Official Publications, 1960-1964 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Orientation, n. d. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Oxford University Press. 1964-1977 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Pacific Lutheran Seminary, 1969-1973 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Partners in Reconciliation, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Policy Committee, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Presses, McGraw Hill, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Prospective, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Provost, 1962-1965, (Edward H. Levi) (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Provost, 1962-1965, (Edward H. Levi) (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Public Relations Office, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Random House, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Rainey, 1906, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Reed College, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Rothko Foundation, n. d. (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Santa Clause, n. d. (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Seminar on Professions, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Southern Methodist University, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - TIAA/CREF, 1971-1972 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Student Organizations, Miscellaneous, n. d. (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Student Organizations, Correspondence, 1956-1965 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Students, Civil Rights Bill, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Students, Divinity School Association, 1960-1961 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Student Crisis, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Student Crisis, 1968-1969 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Students, Visnick Rank Protest, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Student Sit-In Aftermath, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Student Uproar, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Student Uproar, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Student Action, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Students, Southeast Asia Studies (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Student Procedure Sheet (blank), n. d. (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Student Aid, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Students, Past Examinations, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Students, Past Examinations, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Student Association, Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Student Council, Ministry Studies Board, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Student Participation Controversy, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Students, Biblical Language Exam Questions, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Survey of Earned Doctorates, 1966-1967 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Swift Hall Facilities, 1961-1964 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Society for Theological Discussion, 1963-1964 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Southeast Chicago Commission, 1956-1964 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Suenens Dinner, RSVPS, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Suenens Dinner, RSVPS, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Suenens, Press Materials, 1964-1965 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Suenens, Faculty Panel, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Suenens, Invitation to Discussion, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Suenens, Photos (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Suenens, Correspondence,, 1964-1966 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Suenens, Interview, n. d. (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Suenens, Report, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Suenens, Criterion Issue, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Suenens, Dinner, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Suenens, Luncheon, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Suenens, Lecture Poster, n. d. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Theological Education Commission, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Thank you letters, Brauer, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - University Bookstore, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - University College, 1962-1963 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - University Community Office, 1962-1966 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - University Senate, Council of the, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - University of Notre Dame, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Urban Training Center, 1967-1969 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Visiting Committee, Divinity School, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - World Association of Theological Schools, 1960-1962 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - World Council of Churches, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Wall Street Journal, Clippings, 1070 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Women's Lib., Teachers, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Theological Education Conference, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Unification Report, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - University of Chicago, Biological Sciences, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - University of Chicago, Statistics and Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - University and Civil Rights, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - University of New Mexico, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - University of Virginia, Visiting Committee, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - University of Virginia, Visiting Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Vesper Intern Program, 1970-1981 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - World Population, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Westminster Press, 1975-1980 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 2: Faculty Materials
    - Faculty Papers, A (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Papers, Ba (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Papers, Be-Bu (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Papers, D (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Papers, H (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Papers, K (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Papers, L (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Papers, M (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Papers, N (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Papers, O (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Papers, P (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Papers, R (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Papers S (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Papers, T (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Papers, W (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Conference, 1966-1967 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Conference, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Series V: Research and Course Notes, 1938-1975
  Series V contains Brauer's research and course notes from 1938 to 1975. Subseries I contains notes, draft chapters, and correspondence relating to Brauer's dissertation, "Francis Rous, Puritan Mystic, 1579-1659: An Introduction to the Study of the Mystical Element in Puritanism," which he completed in 1949 at the University of Chicago.
  Subseries 2 contains notes and documents relating to Brauer's research in religious history, particularly the history of Puritanism, revivalism, and mysticism. The course also contains notes for courses taken by Brauer as a graduate student in the Divinity School, notes and syllabi for classes given by Brauer, and some syllabi for classes given by other faculty members.
  - Subseries I: Dissertation Notes and Drafts
    - Dissertation Notes, n. d (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Dissertation Notes, n. d (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Dissertation Notes, n. d (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Dissertation Notes and Correspondence, 1948 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Dissertation Introduction, n. d. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Dissertation Draft, Part One, n. d. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Dissertation Draft, Part Two, n. d. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Dissertation Draft, Chapter Two, n. d. (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Dissertation Draft, Chapter Two, n. d. (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Dissertation Draft, Chapter Three, n. d. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Dissertation Notes, Chapter Four, n. d. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Dissertation Notes, Chapter Five, n. d (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Dissertation Draft, Chapter Five, n. d. (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Dissertation Notes, Chapter Six, n. d (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Dissertation Draft, Chapter Six, n. d. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Dissertation Notes, Chapter Seven, n. d (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Dissertation Draft, Chapter Seven, n. d. (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Dissertation Notes, Chapter Eight, n. d (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Dissertation Notes, Miscellaneous, n. d. (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Dissertation Notes, Introduction, n. d. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Dissertation, Chapter Five, n. d (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Dissertation Notes, Chapter Nine, n. d. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Dissertation Notes, Conclusion, n. d (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Dissertation Notes, Miscellaneous, n. d. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 2: Research Documents and Notes
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1950s (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Lecture Notes, 1950s (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Notes, n. d. (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Slavery and Religion Research Documents, n. d. (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Shakers Research Documents, n. d. (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Christianity, American Frontier Documents, n. d. (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - American Religious History, Documents, n. d. (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - American Religious History, Documents, n. d. (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - American Religious History, Documents, n. d. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - American Religious History, Documents, n. d. (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - American Religious History, Documents, n. d. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - American Religious History, Documents, n. d. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - American Religious History, Documents, n. d. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - American Religious History, Documents, n. d. (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - American Religious History, Documents, n. d. (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - American Religious History, Documents, n. d. (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - American Religious History, Notes, n. d. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - American Religious History, Notes, n. d. (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - American Religious History, Notes, n. d. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - American Religious History, Notes, n. d. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - American Religious History, Notes, n. d. (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - American Religious History, Notes, 1950s (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Huntington Library Notes, n. d. (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Luther Manuscript, notes and Correspondence, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - American Religious History, Documents, n. d. (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - American Religious History, Documents, n. d. (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Classes to be Given, n. d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - History Notes, 1955-1970 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Lecture Notes, 1948 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Notes to be Sorted Out, n. d. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Notes to be Sorted Out, n. d. (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Notes to File, n. d. (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Conference Notes, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Notes, n. d. (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - New Books Bibliography, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Luther Treatise, Notes, n. d. (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Church History, Bibliographies, n. d. (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Slavery and Servitude, Bibliography, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - English Reformation Notes, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Notes, n. d. (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Notes, Deansley, Medieval, n. d. (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Lectures, English Reformation, 1951 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Religious Liberty Notes, n. d. (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Church and Society, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Protestant church and Society, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Church and Society, Roman Catholicism, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Roman Catholic, Religious Life and Experience, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Church History, Notes, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Reformation Colloquium, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Islam/Judaism, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Religion in Western Culture, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Lectures, Luther, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Religion in Western Culture, Luther, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Reformation, Luther, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Radical Reformation, Anabaptists, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Reformation, Religion and Culture, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Mystical Reformation, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Reformation, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Continental Reformation, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Calvin, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Church, Society, and History, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Modern Christianity, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Reformation Papers, n. d. (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Modern English (British), n. d. (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Modern Europe Notes, n. d. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Deism Notes, n. d. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - England Modern, n. d. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - England Modern, n. d. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Church History English, Modern Liberalism, n. d. (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Modern History of Christianity, n. d. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Krauth, Charles Porterfield, n. d. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Church History Articles, Early Modern Britain, n. d. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Church History Articles Continued, n. d. (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Laud, Notes and Articles, n. d. (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Bishop Andrews, Sermons, n. d. (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Bishop Andrews, n. d. (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Notes, English Church, n. d. (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Notes, English Church, n. d. (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Laud, Notes and Sermons, n. d. (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Puritanism Articles with Notes, n. d. (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Puritanism Articles with Notes, n. d. (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Puritanism Articles with Notes, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Notes on Art, n. d. (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - New Testament Gospels, Hays, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - New Testament Galatians/Romans, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Old Testament Exegesis, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Theology, Systematic, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Historical Theology, Augustine, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Historical Theology, History of Doctrine, Roth, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Confessions, Roth, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Church History, Modern, Roth, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Historical Theology, History of Ancient Theology, Gordh, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Constructive Theology, Brunner, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Dogmatics II, Raun, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Dogmatics I, Raun, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Philosophy of History, Analytical, Evjen, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Historical Theology, The Councils, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Historical Theology, Doctrine of the Person of Christ, n. d. (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Luther, Nature of the Church, Raun, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Temple, Doctrine of the Church, Sugeno, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Church History Survey, McNeil, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Church History Survey, Notes, 1948-1949 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Church History Ancient, Hellenistic Culture, Marcus, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Transcendentalism and Bushnell, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Church History; Religion in America, Survey Notes II, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Church History; American/National, Mead, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Theology; Historical Modern, Gordh, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Religious Thought; Meecham, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Bates, The American Faith, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Church History; Modern American Lutheran, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Marty, Dwight and the Theocratic Ideal, n. d., Folder14: Church Music, History of, n. d. Folder15: Ethics; Raun, Notes, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Church History; Ancient, Origins and Backgrounds, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Church History; Notes, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Medieval Notes, n. d. (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Church History Notes, Reformation, n. d. (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Church History 301, Notes, 1949-1956 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Church History 301; Lectures, n. d. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Church History, Modern Europe, Notes, n. d. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Church History, Modern Europe, n. d. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Church History Notes; Medieval, 1944-1945 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Church History Notes, Reformation, 1941 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Historical Theology Notes, n. d. (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Puritanism, English; Historical Development to 1688, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Calvin Notes, n. d. (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - History Notes, Modern Europe, n. d. (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - History; English Survey, n. d. (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - New Testament Notes, Hays, n. d. (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - New Testament Notes, Epistles, n. d. (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Bibliography Notes, n. d. (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Clipping, 1949 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Comparative Religion Notes, n. d. (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Eastern Philosophy Notes, 1942 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Comparative Theology Notes, n. d. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Philosophy of History Notes, 1941 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - History of Missions Notes, n. d. (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - History of Missions Notes, 1938-1943 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Church History, n. d. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Church History, n. d. (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Church History, n. d. (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Church History, Race Problems, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Church History, Ecumenical, 1948 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Church Fathers, Notes, n. d. (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Dante Notes, n. d. (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Church History, Slavery, n. d. (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Church History, Bibliographies, n. d. (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Philosophy of History, n. d. (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Theology, Old Testament, 1954 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Theology, Old Testament, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Old Testament Notes, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - British Literature Notes, 1938 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Theology Notes, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Church Architecture, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Richard Hooker Notes, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Sociology Notes, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Hebrew Notes, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Liturgics Notes, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Logic Notes, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Theology, New Testament, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Greek Notes, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - American History Notes, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Sermons, Notes, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Sermons, Notes, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Sermons, Pamphlets, 1943-1948 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - New Testament Notes, n. d. (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - New Testament Notes, 1937 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - International Relations Notes, 1942 (Box 75, Folder 4)